This time Satan returns the call…
976-Evil II is a horror film directed by Jim Wynorski.
After being bestowed with demonic powers following a phone call to Hell, a psychotic teacher begins a rampage of death and
destruction in a small town, forcing a teen and her boyfriend to fight him off so that they can get away.
Robin Jamison, played by Debbie James.
Mr. Stephen Grubeck, played by René Assa.
Spike Jones, played by Patrick O'Bryan.
Paula, played by Leslie Ryan.
Dr. Jamison, played by Rod McCary.
Stone, played by Paul Coufos.
976-EVIL II (also known as 976-EVIL 2: The Astral Factor) is a 1992 American
direct-to-video supernatural horror film directed by Jim Wynorski.
The film is a sequel to the 1988 horror film 976-EVIL.
It was referenced in Invasion of the Scream Queens (1992).
The film explores themes of satanism, horoscope, sequel, killer, super power.
The tone is dark.